Now that the training job is finished,
训练完毕后
we can look and scroll through and see all sorts of
我们可以滚动浏览下各种输出结果
output describing how XGBoost is improving at every round,
看看 XGBoost 在每一轮是如何改进模型的
and at the very end telling us the total number of seconds that we are billed for.
最后是计费总秒数
So, now, we have a fit model,
拟合好模型后
and what we'd like to do is test it out on the testing data set.
我们将用测试集测试模型
To do this, we're going to use SageMaker's batch transform functionality.
我们将使用 SageMaker 的批量转换功能
Now a batch transform essentially means that we want to hand it
批量转换是指向 SageMaker 提供一批数据
a whole bunch of data and have SageMaker figure out how to split that data up,
让 SageMaker 去判断如何拆分数据
how to send it to our model,
如何将数据发送给模型
and how to merge all of the results.
以及如何合并所有结果
We will see a little later how we can do that
稍后我们将学习如何手动完成这一过程
ourselves and get a little more insight into what SageMaker is doing in the background,
并了解 SageMaker 的后台运行原理
but for now, we can just view this as another convenient black box.
暂时可以将其看作一种便利黑匣子
So, to do that, we can start by using our estimator object that we created and then fit,
首先使用创建的 estimator 对象 然后拟合数据
and calling the transformer method,
并调用 transformer() 方法
which creates for us a new transformer object.
该方法会为我们创建一个新的 transformer 对象
The only thing that we have to provide is,
我们只需指定
how many virtual machines we want that transformer to use in
转换器要在后台使用多少个虚拟机
the background and what sort of virtual machine we want the transformer to use.
以及要使用什么类型的虚拟机
Again, we only need one for our purposes,
我们只需 1 个虚拟机
and ml.m4.xlarge is wonderful for our use.
并且使用 ml.m4.xlarge 类型就行了
Now that the transformer has been created,
创建好转换器后
it's time to actually start the transform job.
就可以开始转换作业了
Now, what we do is we give it a location.
我们需要提供
This is the data that we saved,
数据的存储位置
the test data that we saved from S3.
即在 S3 中存储的测试数据
We tell it what kind of data it is.
告诉转换器数据类型是什么
In our case, it is CSV data.
对我们来说 是 csv 文件
Further, we tell it how,
此外
if it needs to,
我们可以告诉转换器
it can split the data up.
如何拆分数据
Our data is tabular,
我们的数据是表格形式
which means that each line is its own sample.
所以每行都是独立的样本
So, if it needed to break the data up into chunks,
如果要拆分数据
it could do so by splitting it up by line.
可以按行拆分
Interesting to note is that this cell has now completely executed,
注意 这个单元格现在已经执行完毕了
and what is happening is that SageMaker in the background is creating a transformed job,
SageMaker 在后台创建了转换作业
which it will then run for us.
然后运行该作业
But inside of the notebook,
但是在 notebook 中
we don't really have any indication as to what's going on.
我们并不知道发生了什么
However, if we call it the wait method,
如果调用 wait() 方法
this provides us with some output to give us
该方法会提供一些输出
an indication as to how the transformation job is progressing,
告诉我们转换作业是如何进展的
and in addition, it will let us know when it has finished.
此外 它会告诉我们何时运行完毕
So, for now, we'll just wait for this to finish.
暂时先等待执行完毕
So, another batch transform has completed. So, what happened?
另一个批转换作业运行完毕了发生了什么
Well, SageMaker took our testing data,
SageMaker 获取测试数据
sent it to the model.
将数据发送给模型
The model then performed inference for each sample.
模型根据每个样本做出推理
SageMaker collected all of these predictions up and created a new file,
SageMaker 收集所有这些预测并新建一个文件
and saved that file on S3.
将该文件保存到 S3 上
The location of that file is stored in the xgb_transformer.output_path variable,
该文件的位置保存在 xgb_transformer.output_path 变量中
and we can use a little bit of notebook magic to use
我们可以利用 notebook 命令 aws s3
AWS's S3 functionality and copy the output file to our notebook instance,
将输出文件复制到 notebook 实例中
so we can more easily play around with it.
这样便于处理该文件
Now the output file has been saved inside of
现在输出文件保存到了
the Boston subdirectory of the data directory,
data/boston 目录下
and we can use Pandas to read that CSV file in.
我们可以使用 Pandas 读取该 CSV 文件
Then, we can create a nice little graphic to show how well our model is doing.
然后可以绘制一个图表 看看模型的表现如何
We would expect in a perfect world where we had a model that worked
在理想世界中 模型 100% 预测正确
100 percent of the time that this would be a line y equals x.
这时候是一条直线 x=y
The data here kind of doesn't exactly lie along that line,
数据点并没有完全落入该直线上
but it does mostly,
但大部分都在直线附近
and so we can maybe view this as
看来模型成功了
being a success but that there's some room for improvement.
但是还有改进的余地
As a last optional step,
最后一步是可选步骤
we created a bunch of data and saved it inside of the data directory.
我们创建了大量数据并将其保存到 /data 目录中
If we were to just leave that data there
如果我们将数据留在那
and continue working through the various notebooks,
继续使用各种 notebook
eventually the disk space that we have
最终 notebook 实例上的
available on our notebook instance would be used up.
磁盘空间将耗尽
When that happens, you can get some errors that are a little hard to diagnose.
发生这种情况后 会出现一些很难诊断的错误
So, as a last step here,
最后一步
we're going to clean up that data directory and then remove the directory.
我们将清理该目录 然后删除该目录
That's it. That's our first example.
搞定这就是我们的第一个示例
So, in the next video,
在下个视频中
we are going to take a look at a mini-project for you to do.
我们将介绍需要你来完成的迷你项目